Tree "They're at my parents' house...w Wow, that's too big...w
Takaji "Big! Ji" "We really shouldn't do this kind of thing..." Takaji "You're really fast..." Jessie "Wow, and these slippers are so uncomfortable.
Takaji "You're really fast! Jesse "Wow, and these slippers are really comfortable.
Jessie "Wow, you're so fast!
Jesse "Here's another fast one..." Tatsuki "It smells like my parents' house..." Jesse "Oh, it smells like my parents' house..." Tatsuki "I'm a parent's fool.
Jesse "But I hate it when I come home this early every time.
Jesse "Hey, you guys, get in the picture! Takaji "They're here today...me..." Takaji "Wait a minute.
Takaji "Wait a minute, this guy blends in really fast.
Jesse "Seriously, one time when he came to our house, he said, "Laugh at me, Grandma. Jesse "I said, "Grandma, you're about to have a drink.
Takaji "hahahaha w Today's movie is about the members staying at my parents' house.
Takaji "Well, I'd like to spend a little free time with the members and make a little video.
Takaji "Well, I guess you can see a lot in this video.
Takaji "What? A script? This looks like a drama script. Impossible. Thin Hanning Flag.
Takaji "The Lady Goya on the clock...what? What?
Takaji "This one too! Jesse "It's a shrimp book! Jesse "It's a shrimp book! Takaji "It's a shrimp book!
Jesse "What? Jesse "Wow, it's amazing!
Takaji "This is so stylish! What's this?
Takaji "What's this? What is this? Is this Mr. Hichou? Jesse "What kind of... what kind of... how do you say?
Takaji "A kid model... like a kid model at a hair salon. Jesse "Oh, I see.
Takaji "Oh, you're not a girl? Jessie "Yes, she is a girl. She likes good looking guys because she's a girl.
Jesse "Well, I don't know who you look like, so I'll see you in Shunta.
Takaji "You smell nice. You're wearing perfume. You smell nice.
Takahashi: "Isn't that our smell?
Inogari I already have garlic on my hands.
Inoue It's like your smell, isn't it?
Takahashi: It's nice.
Takahashi It's really nice.
Inoue I-chan seems to like you more than you think.
Inogari I wonder how I-chan likes him.
I wonder if she's scared of him.
Inokari: I-chan, right.
Takahashi: She's a little shaken up.
Inoue: That could be good.
Takahashi: They smell so good!
Inoue, all of you. Inogari, I've never seen anything like this.
Inoue, Inohari. I wish I could understand your pain.
Inogari, let the voice of your heart echo!
The important thing is...
It says "now".
It's right here.
Takahashi, wait!
Takahashi What's this?
Inoue There was some paper on the table.
Inoue I remember writing this.
Inoue I'm sorry...
Inoue The hearing office.
Takahashi I'm sorry, but I think I wrote this in junior high school.
Takahashi: The hearing office, right?
Inoue Wait a minute!
Inoue, wait a minute.
Takahashi! What?
Inoue What?
Inoue I'll read it.
Inoue Read it so it doesn't come out.
Inoue A good father in the future.
Inoue Someone who's going to be a mom.
Takahashi. What's this?
Inoue, you're in second place.
Takahashi And then there's this...
Takahashi And the other one who seems to be fulfilling his dreams in the future.
Hayato is in third place.
Inoue Oh, third place.
Stop asking and answering.
Inoue Are you an idiot?
Takahashi: What about the one Hayato wrote?
Inoue No, that's too bad.
Takahashi, wait a minute. I can't get it off.
Inoue, wait a minute. I'll show you.
It's not that it's bad, it's just embarrassing.
Takahashi: Then it's okay.
Inoue Oh, there it is!
Takahashi, wait a minute!
Inoue Title?
Inoue Everyone draws a picture of themselves, or a picture of themselves 10 years from now.
Takahashi Yes, yes, yes...
Yes, yes, yes.
I want to write down what I'm doing so that my future self won't be embarrassed when he/she reads it.
I want to write down what I'm doing so that my future self can read it and not be embarrassed.
Takahashi What?
Inoue By the way, "making the most of it" is all in katakana.Inoue By the way, the word "Ikasu" is all in katakana.
Takahashi: I'm making the most of it.
Inoue What are you doing now?
Takahashi: You're being asked a lot of questions.
Inoue I don't have a clear dream yet.
Inoue I don't have a clear dream yet, so please choose a job that fits what I'm going to write about. 1.
1. a job I chose for myself 2. a job that is challenging and enjoyable for me
2. a job that is challenging and enjoyable for me
3. a job that can entertain, please and move people
Takahashi: I'm happy for you.
Inoue: You're okay?
Takahashi That makes me cry.
Inoue You're making it happen.
I made it happen 10 years ago.
Now let me summarize what I want you to fix.
1. indecisiveness
Inoue Oh, that's okay.
2. selfishness
Inoue: Oh, that's okay.
Takahashi: It's our turn. 3.
3. a little rebellious
Inoue Oh, that's okay.
He's a little short.
Inoue: It's fixed now.
Takahashi: It's fixed.
Inoue So it's fixed.
Takahashi But now people are calling me a gorilla.
You wrote about your height, too.
How tall are you now?
My ideal height is 5'9".
Inoue What?
Takahashi: I'm a little taller now.
Inoue: Well, I'm only about 9.
Takahashi: I exceeded it.
Inoue, look at this.
Takahashi, how much do you weigh?
Inoue: I weigh 63 kilograms.
Takahashi: Almost.
Inoue You're amazing!
Takahashi, you're dreaming!
Inoue Amazing!
Takahashi So...
Takahashi, I've already rebelled against my parents.
So I asked him if he was bullying his little brother. I asked him.
Inoue: I'm still doing that.
Takahashi I'm not doing it!
Inoue I'm still doing that.
Takahashi: I'm still doing this, especially the bullying of my younger brother.
Inoue And you're not doing it!
Takahashi: He bullies his little brother a lot.
Inoue I'm still talking about it.
Takahashi: Oh, that's right.
One last thing.
You only live once.
Let's do our best so we don't have any regrets.
Takahashi: Oh, I don't understand what you just said...
Inoue I'm the one now...
Takahashi: You're fulfilling your dream... for the most part.
Inoue That's great!
You're fulfilling your dreams, aren't you?
Inoue Junior high school?
Inoue I'm still in ninth grade.
Inoue I'm still in junior high, so I'm still in junior high.
Inoue I think it looks like I failed.
Takahashi It says here that your job is to entertain people.
Inoue That's amazing.
Takahashi Entertaining people means... maybe...
Takahashi There are people who often say they want to help people, like they want to be nurses.
Takahashi: You don't say that, do you?
Inoue No, they don't.
Inoue That's true.
Takahashi: He's an entertainer. He's a real entertainer.
Inoue Let's move to a different room.
Inoue We're all going to sleep in this room.
Inoue Wait a minute.
Inoue You mean we're all going to sleep together?
Takahashi You can do it.
Inoue Well, we've just moved.
Inoue The graduation album.
Inoue I found it.
Takahashi? What?Takahashi: What is it?
Inoue This is it.
Inoue It's a high school.
Takahashi, I can't see it at all!
Takahashi, just watch our reactions.
Inoue, let's go!
Inoue Where's Sanoh?
Takahashi Don't tell me!
Inoue Well, well, well...
Inoue I've seen this before.
Takahashi: That's right.
Inoue This is the best impression.
Takahashi No, this is it.
Inoue That one...
Inoue This bangs are popular.
Takahashi No, no, no, no, Patsy's righteous.
Inoue I have confidence in my eyes.
Takahashi No, no, no, no...
Inoue The correct answer is...
Inoue, this is Inokari.
Takahashi! No! Inoue, Inokari!
Takahashi. Inoue, Wild boar hunting... that's right... you...
Takahashi... I've seen it.
Takahashi, we're in a boys' high school.
Inoue No, no, no, this is fun.
Takahashi
Inogari Scary!
Inogari I got to dance!
Inogari I'm looking forward to seeing you in Kohaku!
Inogari I'm going to go see them.
Takahashi: It says "Kohaku" here too.
Takahashi It's not red and white, is it?
I'm looking forward to seeing you at the Kohaku.
You've been saying that for a long time.
I'm going to become a novelist.
What are you talking about?
Inoue Laughing
Inoue lol
Takahashi, you're not good at making a comment.
Inoue Laughing
Takahashi: Well, that's wonderful.
Inoue Thank you very much.
Inoue That's great!
Inoue Junior high school
Takahashi Junior high school
Takahashi Yes.
Inoue Nice!
Takahashi I found a junior high school, too.
Inoue Junior high school
Inoue, there is.
Takahashi, where's it after that?
Inoue, are you there?
Takahashi, take a look.
Inoue, there you are!
Takahashi, there it is!
Inoue Oh, no.
Takahashi
Inoue He looks like a monkey.
Takahashi, you're so hot.
Inoue It's so sad.
Takahashi: And there's two teachers too?
Inoue, you're today's sub!
Takahashi: He has a strong habit of doing that.
Inoue: No, they're quite strong.
Takahashi: He's like this...
Inoue Yeah.
Takahashi: You know, this teacher must have been really strict with you.
Inoue Laughs.
Inoue My teacher was strict.
Takahashi: Laughing.
Takahashi
Inoue That's why he was so strict.
Takahashi Laughs
Takahashi I think you can make a project like that from your teacher.
Inoue Laughing
Takahashi: You've already said something, Mr. Takahashi.
Inoue Laughing.
Inoue This teacher is not strict.Inoue This teacher is not strict and strict.
Takahashi Oh, it's open.
Inoue Yeah.
But he's getting rounder and rounder.
Takahashi: As you get older...
Inoue Yes, that's right.
Takahashi Yeah, that's right.
Inoue Yeah.
Takahashi: Aren't they a little round?
Takahashi That's true.
Inoue But this one...
Takahashi But I like this hairstyle.
Inoue Yeah.
Takahashi This one.
Inoue I like it.
Takahashi Looks popular.
Inoue That see-through rail is fine.
Takahashi Mr. Inokari
Takahashi I really like this quote.
Takahashi: "Good bye is all there is to life.
Inoue I see.
Takahashi Why?
Inoue Good bye is all there is to life.
Takahashi No, you don't usually say that.
Takahashi You don't usually say that.
Inoue It means something sad, doesn't it?
Takahashi Yeah.
Takahashi But I don't know...
Takahashi But it will lead to your growth.
Takahashi That's what it means.
Inoue It's about meeting and parting.
Takahashi That's right.
Inoue That's true.
That's a good word.
Takahashi That's a very nice word.
Takahashi It's too soon.
Takahashi, I'm at my limit.
Takahashi, are you hungry?
Inoue, I'm hungry.
Takahashi, I'm sleepy and hungry.
Inoue I'm hungry.
Takahashi
Takahashi Let's start from here.
Takahashi: I heard you have a lot of memories of Sano-san.
Takahashi
Takahashi I'm going to find something interesting.
Takahashi Let's do it.
Inoue Okay, a game.
Inoue Okay.
Takahashi: I'm the director?
Miki Takahashi
Inoue Yeah.
Inoue What's that?
Takahashi What?
Takahashi, what?
Inoue, Miki bought an expensive one.
Takahashi Yeah.
Inoue Yeah.
It's been a whole year since the audition.
Thank you very much for your hard work.
Takahashi
Inoue Miki bought an expensive one.
Takahashi Yeah.
Inoue Yeah.
Takahashi James?
Takahashi Oh!
Takahashi Oh, Takahashi.
Takahashi That's great.
Inoue, James, maybe.
Inoue, is that your radius?
Takahashi? Just at that time?
Takahashi: Nagasaki's radius?
Takahashi Why did you do this to me?
Takahashi Wow!
Inoue That's crazy.
Takahashi What? You're so beautiful!Takahashi What? You're so beautiful!
Takahashi, what's with the knee?
Inoue: What?
Takahashi: Knees?
Inoue I had knee pain when I was in soccer team... and I had to push it when I was growing up.
Takahashi: Oh, yes, that's right.
Takahashi: That's a bad idea.
Takahashi That's not good.
Inoue Oh no, no, no!
Takahashi I opened the letter at random.
Inoue Here it is.
Inoue Cute!
Takahashi, so cute!
Inoue Too cute!
Takahashi: Whoa, Pearl!
Inoue, there's a phone call for you.
Inokari It's so sharp.
Inoue His fingers are...
Inogari, only doodles!
Inoue Ha-ha-ha!
Inogari You didn't take any pictures?
Takahashi What's that?
Inoue Isn't that too pointy?
Takahashi That's too pointy!
Inokari It's like that.
Inoue No, but...
Takahashi No, but...
Inoue No buts...
Inoue No, no, but
Takabashi No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no
Inoue No, no, no...
Takabashi No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no...
Takahashi No, I think I threw it all away...
Inokari I don't know about that anymore...
Inokari I appreciate it but...
Inogari I was going to throw it away because it's no use leaving it behind...
Inokari I took it for today.
Takahashi: No, that's exactly what I meant.
Takahashi: You're amazing!
Takahashi I've been thinking about YouTube since I was in elementary school.
I've been thinking about it ever since I was in elementary school.
All this time...
All the way...
Takahashi.
Always...
Inohari ever.
Inohari, stay.
Takahashi...
Takahashi Oh, you mean you threw them all away?
Inogari... No...
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no...
Takahashi: Seriously, I didn't get any.
Inokari Zero.
Takahashi: No, maybe.
Takahashi: No, probably not.
Takahashi You got one.
Inogari My one or two, maybe.
Inogari They might be in the box.
Takahashi...
Inokari No, I threw it away...
Inokari Then let's have dinner.
Takahashi Okay...
Thank you for all the memories.
Takahashi Thank you very much.
Inokari Please look at the next sharp.
Takahashi, we're going to have dinner by the campfire after this.
No, no, no, no...
Takahashi: No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Takahashi: I'm not going to burn it.
Takahashi... I'm not going to burn it! I won't burn it!
Takahashi, I'm sorry I took the liberty of going public.
I'm sorry.
Takahashi I think it was an accident...
Takahashi.
I think it was an accident.
I'm here now........
Inokari Thank you so much for preparing it.Inokari Oh, thank you so much for preparing this for us.
Takahashi: Can I say one thing?
I've never seen anything like this in my life.
Inokari, it's so stylish!
Inoue. How cute!
Takahashi, are you going to shake it?
Inogari, Grandma!
Inoue, Grandma!
Grandma!
I've never seen anything like this.
Inoue Thanks, Grandma!
Inoue Thanks for the drink.
Takahashi, thank you.
Thank you for the food.
Takahashi, let's eat!
Inoue, please wait for me.
Inoue, thanks for the food!
Inokari, put some effort into it.
Inoue It's good!
Inoue Wow! Roast beef ramen!
Takahashi: We need more cider!
Inoue Oh yes, Mr. Inokari, you're right about the cider!
Takahashi: Yeah, seriously!
Inoue But you haven't been bullied much, have you?
Hey!
That was a little...
It's okay, it's okay, it's okay.
It's something, isn't it?
More than I agree with you... that's what I remember most.
I wish you'd tell me.
I don't remember it either.
I used to do that.
They still do it to us.
That's what we're doing right now.
We do?
We do it all the time.
You and Jin...
We didn't used to be so close.
No, it just happened yesterday.
Mr. Daichi...
He left an ear of pizza.
And Jutaro...
Jutaro said he was too embarrassed to eat it.
Excuse me, excuse me, sir.
This is Daichi's.
That's so tacky!
These are the ears that Mr. Daichi left behind.
What a pain in the ass!
You don't know what you're talking about.
You
I don't know...
It must be some kind of weird switch that turns me on.
Now that I think about it
I remember when we were going to Nagoya.
I remember crying so hard.
When I visited my grandma and grandpa...
When I went to visit my grandma and grandpa...
You cry a lot now.
Yeah, I guess so.
No kidding.
Surprisingly, I haven't cried as much as I have when I've invited you as a member.
I didn't cry the most.
You did.
I'm not crying.
Why aren't you crying, guys?
Jate never cries.
Have you ever seen him cry even once? I have.
Once or twice.
Once?
Oh, twice.
Twice.
No, that's probably because you didn't send me a proper save.
I didn't send in the proper saves.
Uh, my emotions are already following me.
What? Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Emotions now.
It's getting a little sad.
You were in eighth or ninth grade.
You were doing it all by yourself until you moved to Tokyo.You did it all the time, all by yourself, until you moved to Tokyo.
And then you wouldn't be lonely anymore.
Well, that's true.
I see.
You managed to get the money fast.
It was fast.
I guess it was fast.
I haven't cried much lately.
That's true.
You used to cry a lot.
I used to be the first one to cry.
I used to cry at the end of Lily's eyes.
That's right.
Smile.
For example.
I was in Rebellion Avant-garde Lily.
And on the last day of the re-release...
We're going to release another single, and we've already started recording it.
You were crying.
"It's going to end.
But the schedule was hard.
I could finally finish.
It was so hard.
I cry even when I'm really sick.
You tend to cry, don't you?
You tend to cry.
Crier.
When I was an aunt, I cried like a fool.
You cried a lot.
Games are fun, aren't they?
I'm a trainer.
Do you want a chocolate mint crepe?
Yes, that's me.
That's my trainer.
Wow, I already have one I love so much.
Grandma, get me all different flavors.
Omitsu has to go to a meeting.
Okay.
I'm going back to the hotel.
I have another meeting in the morning.
That's right.
I'm going back to the hotel.
So, good night, Omitsu.
Bye-bye.
Thank you.
Good luck.
Checkmate, please.
Bye-bye.
He's asleep.
Shibuya Taku has reached his limit. The leader is taking a bath now.
I'm going to crown him too. It's 4:00 p.m.
Bye bye!
The last group.
Have you ever seen makeup like this? I've never seen anything like it.
Oh, my God.
Time.
Five o'clock.
Iwamoto, you're lying!
Fukazawa, since there are four of us...
Let's play rock-paper-scissors to decide where to go!
Iwamoto, that's not so bad.
Fukazawa, it's the most important game of rock-paper-scissors-scissors.
Iwamoto, 13?
Fukazawa, bed 1, bottom 3, right?
Iwamoto, that's right.
Sakuma, oh my garting!
Fukazawa, first, "Goo" rock-paper-scissors-scissors.
Fukazawa, eye cushion.
Iwamoto, eye cushion.
Fukazawa, eye cushion
Iwamoto, orders.
Fukazawa, it's over.
Sakuma: Unusual.
Fukazawa, first, "goo" rock-paper-scissors...
Fukazawa, all right!
Fukazawa, here we go. The center is decided.
Seino
Yes!Yes!
It's a little loud.
Ready, goo, giant poi.
I got it.
Oh, no.
Oh, no!
That's not good.
Oh, no.
Why?
Guys between the ages of 20 and 25...
Sleeping with their faces in their hands
No, when I'm in the middle...
You're late! With Jin...
How did you do it?
Kaito Miyachika, can you turn off the light?
Yes, I'll turn them off!
Thank you, Kaito Miyachika.
I'll see you in two hours.
Yes, sir.
I look forward to working with you.
Excuse me.
Leave it on for a minute.
If I turn it off, you might get mad.
I'm dying.
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
I'm gonna die. I'm gonna die. I'm gonna die.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no!
Three, two, one.
Phew.
Shintan.
We're running out of time.
Why?
Because...
Because you're asleep.
I'll go.
If you haven't come out of bed in 15 minutes.
I'm gonna come back and throw water on you.
Okay. - Okay.
It's cold.
Good night, sweetheart.
Mmm.
Awww... Awww...
He's dead.
We're running out of time.
10 minutes.
Matsuda, I hit my hip!
Nakamura, I hit him in the hip!
Matsuda, let's see...
Matsuda, I'm leaving for my parents' house in Sano
Nakamura, thank you very much
Matsuda, thank you very much
Nakamura, thank you for your help
Matsuda, I'm off
Nakamura, bye-bye
Nakamura I'm off
Nakamura Bye-bye!
Matsuda Come again!
NakamuraYes, I'm here!
Nakamura Bye-bye!
Nakamura, Taku
Nakamura, bye-bye!
Nakamura Taku
Nakamura, Taku looked at me
Matsuda, all right, we're on our way.
Matsuda, we're on our way to Nagoya station
Matsuda, I'm going to shoot YouTube and record
Matsuda I'm going to work a lot
Matsuda I'll do my best!
Matsuda, yay-o!
Here we are!
Yes, thank you very much.
We're here.
Well, I'd like to play rock-paper-scissors for the bullet train back to Tokyo now.Well, I would like to play rock-paper-scissors for the bullet train back to Tokyo now.
Yes, sir.
Well, we've all woken up from sleep.
We're in a bad mood, but even if we lose, we have no complaints.
I see.
Okay.
Okay, goo, goo.
Here we go, Shun Tan.
Oh, he's sleeping!
You can play rock-paper-scissors in your sleep.
Make sure the camera can see you.
First, goo, then rock, paper, scissors.
Oh, wait.
You did it. You did it.
First, goo, then rock, paper, scissors.
Okay, one.
Okay, okay, okay, three rock, paper, scissors.
First, goo, rock, paper, scissors.
Okay, so I'd like to go back to Tokyo.
Let's go!
You, have a nice time at Emix.